A Finding Aid to the Dorothy Weiss Gallery Records, circa 1964-2001 (bulk 1984-2000), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1979-1999; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 0.75 Linear feet Box 19
  May 4-27, 1995 Jack Earl - Narrative Sculpture
  June 1-July 1, 1995 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
  July 6-29, 1995 Introductions' 95 - Timothy Hower, Helene E. C. Linder
  Aug. 3-Sept 2, 1995 Horse Show
  Sept. 7-30, 1995 Charles Hobson: Clouds & Dreams - Variations on Longitude and Surrealism
  Oct. 5-29, 1995 New Clay - Jeff Irwin, Annabeth Rosen
  Nov. 2-Dec. 2, 1995 Jay Musler - Imaginary Evolution
  Dec. 7-Jan. 27, 1995-96 Teapot Invitational
  Feb. 1-Mar. 2, 1996 Jun Kaneko - Drawings and Sculpture
  Mar. 7-30, 1996 Daniel Brice, Philip Cornelius and James Morris
  Apr. 4-27, 1996 Beveryly Mayeri - New Work
  May 2-June 1, 1996 Michael Lucero - Reclamation Series
  June 6-29, 1996 Jim Melchert and Jamie Walker - "Affinities," Sculpture for the Garden
  July 5-Aug. 3, 1996 Introductions '96 - Masako Miyata, Jenifer Wofford
  Sept. 5-28, 1996 Hank Murta Adams, Pike Powers, James Watkins - Glass Sculpture
  Oct. 3-Nov. 30, 1996 Gregory Roberts - Thirst
  Nov. 7-30, 1996 Dog Show
  Dec. 5-Feb. 1, 1996-97 Annette Corcoran - Icones Avium
  Feb. 6-Mar. 1, 1997 Scott Chamberlin, Annabeth Rosen, Arnie Zimmerman
  Mar. 6-Apr., 26, 1997 Therman Statom - Myths, Science and Nature
  May 1-31, 1997 Doug Jeck - Men and Boys
  June 5-July 5, 1997 Sculptors and Their Drawings - Rudy Autio, Jun Kaneko, & Michael Lucero
  July 10-Aug. 2, 1997 Introductions '97 - Sean Fletcher, Patrick Hilferty, Cassandra Jones, Beth King
  Aug. 7-30, 1997 Chris Silliman, Sergei Isupov - New Clay
  Sept. 4-27, 1997 Charles Hobson: Lighthouse Legends - Works on Paper and Artist's Books
  Oct. 2-Nov. 29, 1997 Clifford Rainey - "Homo Faber," New Sculpture
  Dec. 4-Jan. 31, 1997-98 Teapot Invitational
  Apr. 2-May 2, 1998 Beveryly Mayeri - The Nature Series
  May 7-June 27, 1998 Jun Kaneko - New Work
  July 9-Aug. 1, 1998 Introductions '98 - Elizabeth Ennis, Susan L. Howard, Dharma Strasser
  Aug. 6-28, 1998 The Dimensional Canvas - Painted Studio Glass
  Sept. 3-25, 1998 New Work From Europe - Wouter Dam and Ken Eastman
  Oct. 1-31, 1998 Richard Marquis - New Work
  Nov. 5-28, 1998 Daniel Brice - New Work on Paper
  Dec. 3-Jan. 30, 1998-99 Annette Corcoran - New Work
  Jan. 7-30, 1999 Important Works in Clay and Glass
  Feb. 4-27, 1999 Justin Hunter - Recent Paintings and Drawings; Lawrence LaBianca - Reconnection With Nature
  Mar. 4-27, 1999 Annabeth Rosen - New Work
  Apr. 1-30, 1999 Philip Cornelius - New Work
  May 6-29, 1999 Doug Jeck - Recent Sculpture
  June 3-30, 1999 Jean-Pierre Larocque - New Work
  July 8-31, 1999 Introductions '99 - David King, Barbara Hashimoto
  Aug. 5-31, 1999 Stephen Bradford - Figurative Sculpture, William Samios - New Paintings
  Sept. 9-Oct. 30, 1999 Michael Lucero - Wonderland Series
  Nov. 4-30, 1999 Steven Montgomery - Recent Sculpture
  Dec. 2-Jan. 29, 1999-00 Therman Statom - New Glass Sculpture
  Dec. 2-Jan. 29, 2000 Teapot Invitational
  Feb. 3-29, 2000 Sergei Isupov, Gregory Roberts - New Sculpture
  Mar. 2-31, 2000 Beverly Mayeri - New Sculpture
  Apr. 6-29, 2000 Daniel Brice - Drawings
  Mar. 2-May 20, 2000 Gallery Closing Sale
  - Introductions, 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - New Work for the New Year, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - New Forms In Glass - A Series of Three Exhibitions (1981), 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - West Coast Glass (1982), circa 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
  - Teapot Invitational (1984), 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Glass Sculpture: Five Artists (1985), circa 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Teapot Invitational (1985, 1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - British Ceramics (1986), circa 1983-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 11-13)
  - New Glass (1987), circa 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14-15)
    Includes illustrated letter from Walter Lieberman.
  - The Alfred Show (1989), 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16-17)
  - New Glass (1989), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Teapot Invitational (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Sculpture (1991), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Teapot Invitational (1991, 1992), circa 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Glass Invitational (1994), circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Teapot Invitational (1994, 1996, 1997, 1998), 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Potent Images - Figurative Clay Sculpture (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - The Dimensional Canvas - Painted Studio Glass (1998), circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Important Works in Clay and Glass (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Subject Files, 1983-2000; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 0.45 Linear feet Boxes 19-20
  The subject files that comprise this series include general correspondence concerning gallery activities arranged by type of client, documentation of outgoing and returned loans, and records relating to several projects involving other institutions in which the gallery was involved. The Chicago Art Fair folder contains photographs of Dorothy Weiss Gallery installations at the Fair.
  Records are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Advertisements, 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - American Craft Museum and Council, 1983-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Chicago Art Fair, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Art Consultants, 1990-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Corporate, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Foreign, 1992-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1985-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Twigg-Smith, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Loans for Exhibitions, 1984-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 35-37)
  - Loans Returned, 1982-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - National Museum of History, Taiwan (Marvin Fang), 1992-1995, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco Craft and Folk Art Museum, 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco International Airport, 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Scripps Ceramic Annual (Beveryly Mayeri and Wouter Dam), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Taipei Fine Arts Museum, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Office (Kiyoji Tsuji), 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)